welcome everybody today we are going to
欢迎大家今天我们要
see how to develop your special web
了解如何开发您的特殊网站
service with Kalinin Springwood first
首先与Kalinin Springwood合作
let me to quickly introduce myself
让我快速介绍一下自己
myself so i'm sebastian de ros i live in
我自己，所以我住在塞巴斯蒂安·德·罗斯
new in france like you can hear with my
法国的新事物，就像你可以听到我的
accent i work at pivot era many on
我在支点时代工作的口音很多
spring farm work and on rector my actual
春季农场工作，并指导我的实际工作
focusing is on the reactive supports in
重点放在
Spring Framework 5 I'm a co-worker at a
Spring Framework 5我是一家公司的同事
co-working space called La Cote and I'm
我叫La Cote的共同工作空间
also a staff member of MIT's it
也是麻省理工学院的工作人员
conference which is a conference that's
会议是一个会议
open in France so we are going to
在法国开业，所以我们要
introduce : before to go deeper into the
介绍：在深入之前
details of the application that that we
该应用程序的细节，我们
are going to see so the first question I
将会看到所以第一个问题
would like to ask is why why choosing :
想问一下为什么选择：
there is other languages Serizawa so why
还有芹泽其他语言，为什么
should we use cutting I think the main
我们应该使用切割吗？我认为主要
driver is to overcome the limits of Java
驱动程序是要克服Java的限制
I mean srevice great we all know it very
我的意思是服务很棒，我们都非常了解
well
好
I use it every day to develop spinning
我每天都用它来纺纱
reactor and a lot of projects in in
反应堆和许多项目
pivotal but to develop application
关键但要开发应用程序
service some limits its verbose it has
服务一些限制它的冗长
limited typing friends no properties
限制打字的朋友没有属性
checked exceptions issues with null
检查异常为空的问题
pointer exception the extensibility is
指针异常的可扩展性是
quite quite limited if we compare Java
如果我们比较一下Java的话
to the language like Ruby for example
例如Ruby之类的语言
where we have a pure full extension
我们有一个完整的完全扩展
model there is some issue there
模型那里有问题
semicolon and the end of the lines are
分号和行尾是
just too detailed but that that good
太详细了，但是那很好
matters Java is quite simple but there
Java很简单，但是在那里
is also multiple Java Paseos Java has a
还有多个Java Paseos Java具有
long history and there is a some trap
历史悠久，有一些陷阱
that come from this long history and I
来自悠久的历史，我
really think that we deserve a better
真的认为我们应该得到更好的
solution that Lombok I don't know if you
龙目岛的解决方案，我不知道你是否
Nuremberg but that's that's some
纽伦堡，就是这样
annotations and some Alpers to be able
注释和一些Alpers能够
to write shorter Java code and that's
编写较短的Java代码，那就是
nice but
不错但是
that's still a trick and I think we just
那仍然是一个把戏，我想我们只是
have a better a better solution at the
有更好的更好的解决方案
same time we want to keep what makes a
同时我们要保持使
great service fast it produced optimized
优质的服务，快速，产生了优化
bed code it has a static typing that
床码，它具有静态类型
allow us to have a nice autocomplete in
让我们有一个很好的自动完成功能
the IDE to be able to do a lot of checks
IDE可以进行很多检查
during the compilation especially for
在编译过程中
big projects that very important it's
大型项目非常重要
quite simple to learn and it has an
很简单的学习，它有一个
amazing ecosystem and in spring we are
令人惊叹的生态系统，在 Spring ，
in the second system so we want to keep
在第二个系统中，所以我们要保持
that so I have tried to summarize there
所以我试图在那里总结
what I think has a key point of of : so
我认为有一个重点：
to me Kathleen is an elegant and
在我看来，凯瑟琳是一位优雅而
pragmatic language that allowed to write
允许写的实用语言
concise code and to to write faster your
简洁的代码，以便更快地编写
application there is a big focus on
应用程序着重于
making content easy to read we will see
使内容易于阅读，我们将看到
that later with the code examples
后面的代码示例
reading the code easily is very
轻松阅读代码非常
important because you you write the code
重要，因为您编写代码
one time but after that you and other
一次，但之后你和其他人
people will have to debug that code and
人们将不得不调试该代码，
that's really important to be able to to
能够做到这一点非常重要
read the code easily good clean as an
阅读代码很容易干净
awesome type inference with static
很棒的静态类型推断
typing so really clean as the same level
打字真的很干净
of static typing than Java everything is
静态类型比Java一切都重要
statically typed you don't have some
静态输入您没有一些
magic thing like in in Ruby or
像在Ruby中那样神奇的东西
JavaScript but thanks to it it's clever
JavaScript，但是由于它的巧妙
type in France basically you you you can
基本上在法国输入您就可以
write very short code I mean code key
写非常短的代码，我的意思是代码键
could be as short as in groovy but with
可能和groovy一样短，但是
fully a statically typed API and that's
完全是静态类型的API，那就是
that's very potent containers a very
这是非常有效的容器
good Java interoperability in both ways
两种方式都具有良好的Java互操作性
that's that's a key point especially
这就是关键点
when you want to use cocaine with the
当您想将可卡因与
spring ecosystem there is no safety
春季生态系统没有安全感
extensions DSL all these things we are
扩展DSL所有这些东西
going to
即将
see more in details later and there is
稍后查看更多详细信息
no no more mandatory semicolon at the
不再没有强制性分号
end of the lines good Kirkland I started
行尾好我开始
a few years ago but only came to GA this
几年前，但才来到GA
year so cut clean one dot o has been
这么干净的一年
released at the beginning of this year
在今年年初发布
so that's maybe why it's not as widely
所以这也许就是为什么它不那么广泛的原因
spreaded than other other languages but
比其他语言传播得更多，但是
I don't have exact figures in Tamil
我的泰米尔语没有确切数字
for example github repositories but when
例如github仓库，但是当
I was talking with the dead brain guys I
我当时正在和那些脑筋急转弯的家伙聊天
think the figures are really really
认为这些数字是真的
great and I think yeah I think that's on
太好了，我想是的
a good trend so current latest stable
好趋势，所以当前最新稳定
version is the one that ordered free and
版本是免费订购的版本，
the first cut clean 1.1 preview is
第一个干净的1.1预览版是
available and will continue to ever to
可用，并将继续
be released later that's important to
稍后发布对
understand that the must have the cut
了解必须切
clean application developers come from
干净的应用程序开发者来自
Android world because cut hello to
Android世界，因为您好
generate Java 6 byte code with very nice
生成非常漂亮的Java 6字节代码
languages that we are going to detail
我们将要详细介绍的语言
later
后来
and basically that allow developers to
基本上，这使开发人员能够
welcome to the limitation of the on read
欢迎阅读的限制
platform which was stick to Java 6
坚持Java 6的平台
syntax until on the window gap that is
语法直到窗口间隙
about to be released and even with
即将被释放，甚至与
Android nougats reporter AIDS some Java
Android牛轧糖记者艾滋病一些Java
8 ApS are not available and you can
8 ApS不可用，您可以
generate bytecode for some older version
生成一些旧版本的字节码
of Android so I really think that code
Android，所以我真的认为该代码
clean will continue to be popular in in
清洁将继续在
the Android world and really in the
在Android世界中
Android community cooking is very very
Android社区做饭非常非常
widely used the second use case is the
广泛使用的第二个用例是
use case that we are going to detail
我们将详细介绍的用例
today
今天
that's the server use case using content
这是使用内容的服务器用例
to develop server application instead of
开发服务器应用程序而不是
shut up you can also develop desktop
闭嘴，你也可以开发桌面
application and others like web
应用程序和其他类似Web的应用程序
application we are going or so to see
我们将要看到的应用程序
that later this this diagram shows the
稍后，此图显示了
method
方法
number eight application I don't know if
我不知道是否有八号申请
you are familiar with some redevelopment
你熟悉一些重建
but basically on mobile we are we have
但基本上在移动设备上
limited resources and there is some
资源有限，有一些
limitation in on read about a number of
关于阅读的限制
methods and with very dynamic languages
方法和非常动态的语言
like Ruby the bytecode generated
像Ruby这样生成的字节码
contains a lot of cases a lot of mythos
包含很多案例，很多神话
and you can see in this diagram that the
您可以在该图中看到
number of methods in groovy is very high
常规的方法数量很多
after that color is a little bit better
那颜色好一点之后
and code clean is almost at the same
和代码干净几乎是相同的
level than danjela this number of
级别比danjela这个数字高
methods is after using ProGuard so after
方法是在使用ProGuard之后
removing a news code and basically what
删除新闻代码，基本上是什么
you you you should get in production so
你你应该投产所以
that's also why Kathleen is successful
这就是凯瑟琳成功的原因
in in on the red world that's a low to
在红色的世界里
generate optimized bad code as optimized
生成优化的优化错误代码
as injera almost with a much more
作为注射剂，几乎还有更多
powerful language to continue the
强大的语言继续
compression I have tried to to put a few
压缩我试图把一些
sentences about how does it compare with
与它相比如何的句子
values languages so how does it compare
重视语言，所以它如何比较
with groovy
时髦
I think Kathleen took a lot of things
我认为凯瑟琳做了很多事情
from groovy a lot of IDs they share the
从groovy他们共享了很多ID
same consistent expressive code but the
相同的一致表达代码，但
main differences even is groovy as a
主要的区别甚至是
compiled static mode they were developed
他们开发的静态编译模式
by selection Pope but Kathleen has
通过选择教皇，但凯瑟琳有
released static typing at the core of of
释放了静态打字的核心
the languages and that that makes a lot
语言，这使得很多
of differences in term of autocomplete
自动完成方面的差异
in term of a lot of things that's not an
在很多事情上不是
optional thing that you add later or the
您以后添加的可选内容或
content API is designed to for for
内容API设计用于
static typing where in Ruby world you
静态类型在Ruby世界中的位置
have a lot of dynamic thing like Jesus
有很多像耶稣这样充满活力的东西
reporting like that that only work in
这样的报告只能在
dynamic mode and really in Ruby dynamic
动态模式，实际上在Ruby中
and static mode are really two different
和静态模式真的是两个不同
things
东西
we're in contain shift to to to to allow
我们正在包含转移到以允许
concise code with static
简洁的静态代码
being everywhere and that's that's a key
无处不在，这就是关键
point I think about Kara I have taken
我想起我所学的卡拉
some quotes from a nice blog post from
来自一个不错的博客文章的一些报价
from scar a developer and someone that
从疤痕的开发商和人
really loves Keller that's somebody
真的很喜欢凯勒
working at electronic art I think and
我认为在电子艺术领域工作
the blog post is called the yin and the
该博客文章称为“阴和
yang of programming languages this guy
杨编程语言这家伙
called some people say contain as 80% of
有人说含有80％
the power of Skara with 20% of the
Skara的力量占20％
features and you also say consists of
功能，您还说包括
two engineering language in contrast to
两种工程语言相对
Skara which is a computing science
Skara是一门计算科学
language and I think that's a good a
语言，我认为这是一个很好的
good difference contain is simpler a
好的差异包含比较简单
little bit less powerful more pragmatic
少一点力量，更务实
perhaps more carefully design with JVM
也许使用JVM更仔细地设计
constraints in mind and so both
考虑到限制因素
languages are interesting but as a
语言很有趣，但是作为一种
software engineer as somebody who
作为某人的软件工程师
develops in good application to me
对我很好的发展
cotton is a much more better fit and if
棉花更合身，如果
we compare 14 with swift the languages
我们将14种语言与快速语言进行比较
the language created by Apple to develop
苹果公司开发的语言
iOS application and that is now coming
iOS应用程序即将推出
for developing server-side application
用于开发服务器端应用程序
with IBM and companies like that I felt
与IBM和类似的公司一起
that in terms of syntax Swift and
就Swift和
cocaine are very very very similar you
可卡因非常非常相似
will see that there is a lot of syntax
会看到有很多语法
in command so one of the mains are there
在指挥中，所以其中一个主电源在那里
is a lot of differences but one of the
有很多差异，但其中之一
main is that Swift is 11 based so LLVM
主要是Swift是基于11的，因此LLVM
is byte code where we Lola well coming
是我们Lola即将来临的字节码
from cc precipice world that is data
来自cc绝境世界，即数据
load to generate some native code for
加载以生成一些本机代码
BIOS platforms so that's a kind of byte
BIOS平台，这有点不足
code but more for the compile time not
代码，但编译时间更多
for the execution time so not for the
对于执行时间，而不是
run time and so switched as C and C++
运行时间，因此切换为C和C ++
interoperability where
互操作性
code clean is more gvm based and as very
代码清理更基于gvm，并且非常
good Java interoperability but really
良好的Java互操作性，但实际上
this these two languages are very close
这两种语言非常接近
and I think
而且我认为
these two languages are very great very
这两种语言都很棒
great so this is some code here we have
很好，这是这里的一些代码
a user class which defines four
一个定义四个的用户类
properties user name first name last
属性用户名名姓
name and location so you can see that
名称和位置，以便您看到
with this short syntax that you can find
通过这种简短的语法，您可以找到
something close in scala i at the same
在同一时间在斯卡拉关闭的东西
time additions of a defined to four
定义为四个的时间加法
properties and I also defined the
属性，我还定义了
constructor of this class there is the
这个类的构造函数有
VAR keyword before user name first name
VAR关键字，位于用户名的名字之前
last name and location vast significant
姓氏和位置非常重要
that via the properties me table I could
通过属性表我可以
have used Val to say that property will
用瓦尔说财产会
not we're not very unlike in Java the
不是，我们在Java中不是很像
type is after the name of the property
类型是在属性名称之后
so this will generate the getters and
所以这会产生吸气剂和
setters you don't have to define the
二传手，您不必定义
field and get all the setters that's
领域，并获得所有的二传手
that's all done you can also customize
完成所有操作后，您还可以自定义
the ketosis and the setter and if you
酮症和二传手，如果你
have a look to the last property
看一下最后一个属性
location you will see a question mark
位置，您会看到一个问号
after so point is a is a type with yeah
在这之后是一个是的类型
that's that just a geometry type but
那只是几何类型而已
there is a question mark at the end of
在结尾处有一个问号
the on the type that means that this
在类型上意味着
type is new label because in Catalan by
类型是新标签，因为在加泰罗尼亚语中
default variables or property that you
您的默认变量或属性
define are not available and that check
定义不可用，该检查
during the compilation so everywhere
在编译过程中，到处都是
where you could just a new pointer
在这里你可以只是一个新的指针
exception you will have to under that
例外，你将不得不根据
and by default encoding you can't set
默认情况下，您无法设置
something to know if I add a question
我要添加一个问题才能知道的事情
mark after the type that means that this
在类型之后标记，表示此
type is is is new label basically and
类型是基本上是新标签和
you see that there is equal new at the
您会发现在
end of the line that that means that I
这行的末尾意味着我
am giving a default value for the last
我给最后一个默认值
parameter so in practice that allow me
参数，以便在实践中让我
to to create a user just using user name
仅使用用户名创建用户
first name
名字
last name or by using a fourth parameter
姓氏或使用第四个参数
which is the location and I can do that
这是位置，我可以做到
without redefining an overloaded
无需重新定义重载
constructor that allow us to produce
允许我们产生的构造函数
more concise code that allows to make
更简洁的代码可以使
that code more readable and that's quite
更具可读性的代码
important at the right I think you won't
在右边很重要，我想你不会
be able to read but just to show you the
能够阅读但只是向您展示
same code in Java it's much more longer
Java中的相同代码会更长
we all have ideas that allow us to
我们都有想法让我们能够
generate the Gator setters easily even
甚至可以轻松生成Gator setter
the equals and hashcode methods but my
等于和hashcode方法，但我
point is not here my point is that when
关键不是这里，我的意思是
the time comes to read your code I
是时候阅读您的代码了
really prefer to read a cartoon version
真的更喜欢看卡通版
than the Java version where as a clear
比Java版本更清晰
book could be anywhere and there is a
书可能在任何地方，并且有
lot of code and a lot of noise so so I
很多代码和很多噪音，所以我
can add a data keyword before the class
可以在课程之前添加数据关键字
in order to say that I want also to
为了说我也想
automatically generates equals and
自动生成等于和
hashcode methods
哈希码方法
so that's syntactic sugar that still
所以那句语法糖
allow us to to write more concise code
让我们编写更简洁的代码
coding as optional and named parameters
编码为可选参数和命名参数
so if we have a look to this reformat
所以如果我们看看这个格式
function you see that I have a string
函数你看到我有一个字符串
mandatory parameter and after that I
强制参数，然后我
have four optional parameters they are
有四个可选参数
optional because I define a default
可选，因为我定义了默认值
value so if you don't provide these
价值，因此，如果您不提供这些
parameters the default value will be
参数默认值为
used in Java has done with overloaded
在Java中使用超载已完成
methods and I will have to put a lot of
方法，我将不得不投入很多
a valid method to do that
一种有效的方法
here I can do that with just a single a
在这里，我只需一个
single function definition and so I can
单一功能定义，所以我可以
just go reformat foobar and normalize
只需重新格式化foobar并标准化
case parameter will be set to truth
case参数将设置为true
upper case first letter parameter will
大写首字母参数将
be set to true etc etc the same method I
设置为true等相同的方法我
can call reformat foobar and specify the
可以调用重新格式化foobar并指定
values parameters so that's defined by
值参数，以便由
the opposition
反对派
so in that case you see that to redefine
因此，在这种情况下，您会看到重新定义
to define the value of what separator
定义什么分隔符的值
I'm forced to define the other previous
我被迫定义另一个
parameters even if they don't change
参数即使它们没有变化
even if they keep the default values so
即使他们保留默认值
that's that's not what I do at percent
那不是我所要做的
efficient so container allow you to
高效，因此容器使您能够
specify a parameter by its name when you
在您通过参数名称指定参数时
have a few parameters like here that
有一些像这样的参数
allow you to to specify the rod
允许您指定杆
separator parameter to be estimated
估计的分隔符参数
value without defining the other the
没有定义其他的价值
other one so again that's designed to
另一个是这样设计的
allow you to write concise code and
允许您编写简洁的代码并
readable code you can also customize the
可读的代码，您还可以自定义
other ones that's not the same so new
其他不一样的新东西
safety is very important in cotton in
安全在棉花中非常重要
fact before working with cotton I was
事实上，在我从事棉花工作之前
not sure about the usefulness of this
不确定这样做是否有用
feature I mean we all have issues with
功能我的意思是我们都有问题
new pointer exceptions but yeah while
新的指针异常，但是是的
using cotton while developing contain
在开发容器时使用棉花
applications I really feel that that's
应用程序，我真的觉得那是
one of the most important feature of the
最重要的特征之一
languages so as I said previously if you
语言，就像我之前说的，如果你
don't put a question mark after the type
不要在类型后面加上问号
that means the type is not variable so
这意味着类型不是变量，所以
you won't be able to to put a new value
您将无法赋予新的价值
there and if you had a question mark you
在那里，如果您有问号，
you are able to to put this value to
你可以把这个价值
this property of this variable to nil
此变量的此属性为nil
the IDE gives you some hints to say you
IDE给您一些提示，告诉您
okay
好的
here there is a risk to have a new value
这里有一个新价值的风险
so there is various operator to to to
所以有各种各样的经营者去
provide a default value if if this is
提供默认值（如果是）
noodle or thing like that so you have to
面条或类似的东西，所以你必须
under your self so the fact what should
在你的自我之下，事实是什么
I do if this value is new so if we see
如果这个值是新值，我会做，所以如果我们看到
that example where I create a water
那个我创造水的例子
available in the in the second line of
在第二行
allocation with the points and
用点分配和
question mark so I'm allowed to do that
问号，所以我可以这样做
because the birth birth type our new
因为出生出生类型是我们新的
liberal point basically in the second
自由点基本上在第二
example so location 2 we have the type
例如，位置2我们具有类型
inference that automatically give
自动给出的推论
location to the type a new liberal
一个新的自由派类型的位置
points because well tell the location is
点，因为告诉位置
a new label points here location 2 is
一个新标签指向位置2是
really statically typed it just gets the
真的是静态输入
same type than word to other location
与其他位置的字词类型相同
that's one example of the cutting type
这是切割类型的一个例子
inference and in the location free
推断和位置自由
example here location free is a non new
此处的示例免费位置不是新事物
label point so with Elvis operator we
标签点，所以与猫王操作员
have we are providing a default value so
我们是否提供了默认值，所以
that means that location free will be
这意味着免费位置将是
equals to what other location but if
等于其他位置，但如果
work load application is known the value
应用程序的工作量是已知的值
will will be a point of zero zero zero
将为零零零零的点
so no magic you have to under what to do
所以你不必做什么魔法
if the value is new there is also some
如果值是新的，也有一些
helpers that allowed to avoid new
帮助避免新的帮手
pointer exception so here if it is new
指针异常，所以这里是新的
label and if in this code is location is
标签，如果在此代码中，位置为
nil
零
there won't be any exception troll if if
如果没有，将不会有任何异常巨魔
location is is a value X will be the x
location是一个值X将是x
value that is in location and if
所在位置的价值，以及
vocation is null it will be will be no
职业为空，它将为否
you have similar functionality in groovy
您在groovy中具有类似的功能
and act like that I saw an interesting
像那样，我看到了一个有趣的
example an interesting blog post from
例如来自的有趣的博客文章
Dan Kim from base count that was talking
来自基层的Dan Kim在说话
about how we love the language that we
关于我们如何爱我们的语言
use and so base camp is many ruby
使用，所以大本营是很多红宝石
company and it was a Java developer and
公司，它是一个Java开发人员，
he always wondered why why is this ruby
他一直想知道为什么这红宝石为什么
guys really loves the language
大家真的很喜欢这种语言
and they are really keen on the
他们真的很热衷于
languages and it didn't felt the same
语言，感觉不一样
with Java which which was a language
与Java这是一种语言
that he used in his day-to-day job but
他在日常工作中使用的
it was not able to say that she loved
不能说她爱
Java and and while working with code
Java和使用代码时
clean
清洁
he wrote this blog post and he wrote for
他写了这篇博客文章，并为
many for many years my perspective was
很多年以来，我的观点是
simple I didn't have to love Java or
简单，我不必爱Java或
whatever programming languages to do my
用什么编程语言来做我的
work well that all changed a few months
运行良好，几个月都变了
ago when when you use code clean because
以前，当您使用代码清洁时，因为
basically the language helped him and he
基本上，语言帮助了他，他
really understood finally what the Ruby
终于真正了解了Ruby
guys are that kind of community really
伙计们真的是那种社区
feel so that's hard to explain with
感觉很难用
slides but you I guess you will not feel
幻灯片，但你我想你不会
that when developing some cartoon
当开发一些卡通片时
application so now that we have seen a
应用程序，现在我们已经看到了
quick overview of code clean let's talk
快速清洁代码概述让我们谈谈
about using code clean for developing
关于使用干净的代码进行开发
spring application so a few months ago I
春季申请，所以几个月前
added support for cooking in start just
刚开始就添加了对烹饪的支持
playing the tayo so I guess some of you
玩tayo，所以我猜有些人
already know that's a website that
已经知道那是一个网站
generates project skeleton to start to
生成项目框架以开始
bootstrap your project so if you go to
引导您的项目，所以如果您去
the URL that is at the top of the slide
幻灯片顶部的URL
you will have a crystal form with code
您将拥有带有代码的晶状体
cleaner already selected and you will
已经选择清洁剂，您将
just have to add your dependencies
只需添加您的依赖项
choose maven grader specifies the booze
选择Maven分级机指定酒水
version and that will automatically
版本，它将自动
generates spring boots and cut cane
产生 spring boot 并切成拐杖
project if you go to the regular at the
项目，如果你去常规
spring start that spring data you you
Spring 开始那 Spring 的数据你你
will have to switch to full the full
将不得不切换到完整
version of the form and select go clean
表格的版本，然后选择清理
as at the end instead of Java I have put
作为最后而不是我把Java
some bar codes if you want to do a
一些条形码，如果你想做一个
three-way with your with your mobile I
与您的手机三路同行
think using spring boot and cutting
考虑使用 spring boot 和切割
together make sense because they share
在一起很有意义，因为他们分享
they share the same pragmatic and
他们有着相同的务实和
innovative mindset I mean they are both
创新的心态我是说他们俩
both innovative for example a spring
既创新，例如Spring
boots bring a lot of new stuff
靴子带来了很多新东西
innovation ready
准备好创新
but also we use the eco system we use
但我们也使用生态系统
Java eco system very well and don't try
Java生态系统非常好，不要尝试
to reinvent the wheel so that's why I
重新发明轮子，这就是为什么我
think that innovative and pragmatic and
认为创新务实
and Kelleen is very much about the same
和凯琳几乎是一样的
thing it's about allowing you to write
关于允许您写的东西
efficiently your applications but
有效地应用程序，但是
without creating a wall new eco system
没有创建新的生态系统
where everybody is developing clean and
每个人都在发展清洁
we have seen that in some languages like
我们已经看到某些语言，例如
in Scala of something as to be scary ish
在Scala中有些可怕的东西
to be used if not that does not feel
如果没有使用就不会感到
good and I think cotton is less
好，我认为棉花少了
opinionated about that and hello much
对此很自以为是
mod who to reuse the existing ecosystem
mod谁可以重用现有的生态系统
and that's why that's a good fit with
这就是为什么它很适合
spring which is writen in in Java and we
用Java编写的spring，我们
are we are going to make some
我们要做一些吗
improvement to make using spring and
改进以使用Spring 和
cotton together the best as we can and
尽我们最大的努力
that's what pretty well in fact we when
实际上，这就是我们当
developing some application something
开发一些应用程序
with application with code clean we that
与代码清洁的应用程序，我们
don't feel not designed for that that's
不要觉得不是为那个而设计的
that's pretty nice so I think that one
那很好，所以我认为
of the key point who are why these two
关键点是谁，为什么这两个
technologies used together is is great
一起使用的技术很棒
I'm not here to say that everything is
我不是要说一切都在
perfect
完善
as a result friction points some some
结果摩擦点了一些
have been already fixed some some of
已经修复了一些
them remains so the one of the friction
他们仍然是摩擦之一
points that remains is a little issue is
剩下的一点是一个小问题
with annotations I mean in code in Java
带有注释的意思是在Java代码中
when you have an annotation a real
当您有注解时，
tribute and you want to specify only one
致敬，您只想指定一个
one value for example if you want to
一个值，例如，如果您想
write request mapping method equals
写请求映射方法等于
request method that gets that works
获得有效的请求方法
automatically in Java because in if you
自动在Java中，因为如果
have a loop to request mapping method
有一个循环来请求映射方法
annotation that's that's an array an
注释就是数组
array of request method and if you
请求方法数组，如果您
specify a single value that's fine that
指定一个合适的值
works in Java in cotton and I think
我可以用Java在棉花中工作，我认为
the same in scatter you you have to
同样，您必须分散
specify that's an array of something so
指定这是一个东西的数组
the syntax is a little bit longer in
语法更长一点
Kirkland and that's not very nice
柯克兰，那不是很好
nothing blocking but that's not very
没有什么阻碍，但这不是很
that's not very great to use so there is
使用起来不是很好，所以有
two to one workaround and one refix so
二对一解决方法和一个修复
when workaround for this specific case
在这种情况下的解决方法
which is much more common is to use a
更常见的是使用
new annotation atlases that we have put
我们放置的新注释地图集
in spring framework for that free so in
在春季免费的框架中
spring form of order 3 and 5 and later
3阶和5阶及更高版本的Spring 形式
version you have get mapping past
您过去映射过的版本
mapping but mapping
映射但映射
delete mapping some shortcuts a little
删除映射一些快捷方式
bit like what we you have in the jax-rs
有点像您在jax-rs中所拥有的
world that allow you to specify that
可以让您指定的世界
that's a regular request mapping with
这是一个常规的请求映射
the same options but the method it's
相同的选项，但方法是
fixed to a single get or a single post
固定为单个获取或单个帖子
or single delete and and that's that's
或单个删除，那就是
nice because that that's a way to put a
很好，因为那是一种放置
few specific requests mapping with no
很少有没有映射的特定请求
method basically every method is mapped
方法基本上每个方法都被映射
and that could also cause some
这也可能导致一些
unexpected behavior so that's that
意外的行为就是这样
pretty nice to have this shortcut and
很高兴拥有此快捷方式，
with this shortcut we don't have the
使用此快捷方式，我们没有
array of issue in sprin Kirkland 1.1
sprin Kirkland 1.1中的一系列问题
this issue is likely to be fixed so like
这个问题很可能已经解决，例如
in July you will be able to specify a
在7月，您将可以指定一个
single value for array annotation values
数组注释值的单个值
the second issue is come from a design
第二个问题来自设计
decision from Colleen so there there has
科琳的决定，所以那里有
been a lot of discussion about this
对此进行了很多讨论
particular design point some some people
一些人的特定设计点
are happy with that choice and bhajiya
对此选择感到满意，bhajiya
some are not but in Kirkland
有些不在柯克兰
the classes are final by default you
默认情况下，这些课程是最终的
will see later that canelo some
稍后会看到canelo一些
additional extensibility so but by
额外的可扩展性
default plus classes are finer in Java
default plus类在Java中更好
by default the classes are open and you
默认情况下，类是开放的，您
you have to put final to say ok don't
你必须说最后一点好吧
extend this class don't allow to extend
扩展此类，不允许扩展
this class or don't allow to override
此类或不允许覆盖
this method in contain that's the other
这个方法包含另一个
by default pleasant methods are final
默认情况下，愉快的方法是最终的
and you have to use open keyword to
而且您必须使用open关键字
specify that it should be extended or
指定应扩展它，或
overloaded
超载
why nots but that's not a good fit with
为什么不这样，但这不适合
some mocking libraries or some saturated
一些模拟库或一些饱和的
proxies and in spring we use digital
代理，在春季我们使用数字
proxies we also used other kind of
代理，我们还使用了其他类型的
Jenica demmick proxies but we use some
Jenica demmick代理，但我们使用了一些
jelly proxies so with the current cut in
果冻代理，因此当前切入
one dot Oh
一点哦
how to handle that well first there is
首先要如何处理好
no breaking point you only have to put
没有断点，您只需要放
open keywords and classes and method
打开关键字以及类和方法
level but again that's against the
水平，但这又是对的
spirit of katene that is to allow you to
凯特琳的精神就是让你
write shorter code and that's a little
写较短的代码，这有点
bit annoying to be able to specify to be
有点烦人的可以指定为
forced to specify open for each method
强制为每种方法指定打开
or show configuration passes for example
或例如显示配置通过
so when you can for service and
因此，当您可以提供服务时，
repositories unique and dynamic proxies
存储库的唯一性和动态代理
so that's the default where when you use
所以这是您使用时的默认位置
classes with interfaces because in that
具有接口的类，因为在那
case we are able to use Jade Academy
如果我们能够使用玉学院
proxies and that works perfectly well
代理，效果很好
because that doesn't require you
因为那不需要你
internally to extend the class when
内部扩展类时
that's not possible
那不可能
for example for add configuration or for
例如添加配置或
in some if your service of repository
在某些情况下，如果您的存储库服务
has no interface or thing like that you
没有界面或类似的东西
will have to put the open keyword at
将必须将open关键字放在
class and method level hopefully because
类和方法级别的希望是因为
we have raised that point to jetbrains
我们已经把这一点提到了喷气脑
which developed katene that should be
哪个开发的凯丁烯应该是
fixed in : 1.1 we are we are thinking
固定在：1.1我们正在思考
about values ways to under that one of
关于在其中之一之下的价值观方法
the most most interesting one is to be
最有趣的是
able to provide a meta F file that will
能够提供一个元F文件，该文件将
be in the jars of example in spring Asia
成为亚洲春季的榜样
that could allow us to specify to
可以让我们指定
Kathleen compiler that every class
凯思琳编译器每个类
annotated with add components directly
直接用添加组件注释
or indirectly because I don't know if
还是间接的，因为我不知道
you know but every
你知道，但是每个
at configuration ad series at repository
在存储库中的配置广告系列中
is itself annotated that's all add
本身被注释的全部
components basically because this
组件基本上是因为
annotation are not I did buy at
注解不是我买的
component so if cotton is able to
因此，如果棉花能够
recognize that add component classes
认识到添加组件类
should be opened by default we you won't
应该默认打开，我们不会
have to do all this kind of stuff so we
必须做所有这些事情，所以我们
are trying to find a way to make some
试图找到一种方法使一些
classes annotated by a particular
特定注释的类
annotation open by default for the
注释默认为
compiler I mean in terms of user you
编译器，我的意思是用户
won't be able to extend it but the
将无法扩展它，但是
compiler or during the runtime that will
编译器或在运行时
be possible to extend it there is also
可以扩展它那里
other ways to do that may be some
其他方式可能是一些
compiler plug-in may be some build tool
编译器插件可能是一些构建工具
but my my preferred one currently is the
但我目前首选的是
meta f1 because we just if cutting guys
meta f1，因为我们就像裁员一样
choose to implement that we will just
选择实施，我们将只是
have to add a specific small file in
必须在其中添加特定的小文件
spring in spring job to say to Cochin
春季工作要对科钦说
okay
好的
everything annotated directly or
一切都直接注释或
indirectly by add components should be
通过添加组件间接应
open at runtime and that really is the
在运行时打开，这确实是
main friction point if if these two
如果这两个主要摩擦点
friction points are fixed in coaching
摩擦点在教练中固定
1.1 I mean yeah that that will work
1.1我的意思是那会起作用
pretty well
很不错
that's already what pretty well but
那已经很不错了，但是
that's really my my two main concern I
那真的是我的两个主要问题
have created a spring clean project
创建了一个春季大扫除项目
which is really currently mainly faq so
目前实际上主要是常见问题，所以
I have tried to put some documentation
我试图放一些文件
about this kind of thing friction points
关于这种事情的摩擦点
or some advices about how to how to wait
或有关如何等待的一些建议
spring and curtain application so if you
Spring 和窗帘的应用，所以如果你
have a look if you want to have mod
看看你是否想要国防部
tears about this this these behaviors so
这些行为的眼泪
let's talk about Joe special messenger
让我们谈谈乔特使者
case 2d so just special messenger that's
情况2d所以只是特殊的使者
just a small application
只是一个小应用
a small toy application but I think you
一个小的玩具应用程序，但我想你
will see the source code that's enough
会看到足够的源代码
to show you how to write code clean and
向您展示如何编写干净的代码
spring boot applications so how is
Spring Boot应用程序如何
design this application so it's using
设计此应用程序，以便使用
code clean as a as a language spring
代码干净如语言的 Spring
boot plus t2 SQL as a database open
启动加上t2 SQL作为数据库打开
layers as opening years is a kind of
开放年是一种层次
Google Maps but open source and it
Google Maps但开源及其
allows to you to choose values sources
允许您选择价值来源
of data
数据的
OpenStreetMap Google Maps Bing Maps any
OpenStreetMap Google Maps Bing Maps任何
kind of stuff so you can see that as an
一种东西，所以你可以看到
goggle maps open source so we will have
泳镜地图开源，所以我们将有
so we'll have this JavaScript
所以我们有这个JavaScript
application that we request on the
我们要求的应用程序
server side our convenience reboot
服务器端我们方便重启
application that exposed some rest
暴露了一些休息的应用程序
geez on API that allow us to read free
哎呀，让我们可以免费阅读API
for example the messages and the new
例如消息和新消息
messages that are coming are pushed with
即将到来的消息被推送
server sent events the user location is
服务器发送事件的用户位置是
retrieved with html5 geolocation API we
使用html5地理位置API检索到的
have some pop-ups done with bootstrap so
使用引导程序完成一些弹出窗口，因此
that's a kind of rich rich Internet
那是一种丰富的富互联网
application rich interface application
应用程序丰富的界面应用程序
with with a regular spring boot jeez and
搭配定期的 spring boot jeez和
again the code is available on github so
再次在github上提供了代码，因此
that github.com slashes dollar slashes
github.com大幅削减美元
real special - messenger so you will be
真正的特别-Messenger，使您成为
able to have a look clone it run it on
能够看一下它运行的克隆
your laptop if you want to to try it
您想尝试的笔记本电脑
everything is available and I will try
一切都可用，我会尽力
to keep that up to date with latest
保持最新
spring and continuation and for example
Spring 和延续，例如
when when it will be available - when it
何时可用-何时可用
will be possible to write some classes
可以写一些课
and methods without using the open
和方法不用公开
keyword I will update that I will try to
关键字，我将更新，我将尝试
follow the evolution so let's have a
跟随演变，让我们来
look - this spring MVC
看-今年 Spring 的MVC
cocaine controller so most of the things
可卡因控制器，所以大部分事情
are very closed to vehicular spring
对汽车Spring 非常封闭
emission controls I have tried to
我尝试过的排放控制
highlight the main differences so in
突出显示主要差异
Kirtland classes are public by default
Kirtland类默认为公开
so you don't have to specify the public
因此您不必指定公众
key words the methods are also public by
关键词这些方法也是公开的
default you don't have to specify the
默认情况下，您不必指定
public key word - as of spring from lock
公共关键字-从锁开始的 Spring
for that free and that's not specific to
这是免费的，而这并非特定于
Kathleen but I would like to to talk
凯瑟琳，但我想谈一谈
about that the constructor injection
关于构造函数注入
without at Ottawa Yard is possible if we
如果我们在渥太华场没有
have a single constructor so that's why
只有一个构造函数，所以这就是为什么
there is not a total wired in in the
没有总接线
controller constructor because that's
控制器构造函数，因为那是
like the first example that we have seen
就像我们看到的第一个例子
we are defining at the same time the
我们正在同时定义
constructor and and the properties we
构造函数和属性
are using the method that uses for
正在使用用于
request mapping that we have seen before
请求映射，我们以前见过
to avoid to write array off so we are
避免注销数组，所以我们
using add pass mapping and get mapping
使用添加通过映射和获取映射
advert mapping and that would be the
广告映射，那将是
same in Java again that's not specific
再次在Java中相同，但不具体
to to Kathleen that just allows you to
到凯瑟琳，那只能让你
write shorter code and if you have a
编写较短的代码，如果您有
look to the lists function you will see
查看列表功能，您将看到
that thanks to the type in France we are
由于法国的类型
usually able to write a single meters
通常能够写一个电表
with a single line like that and we
用这样的单行，我们
don't have to specify the type of the
不必指定
rate of the list return value that will
列表返回值的比率
be automatically guests and that will be
自动成为客人，那将是
used that will use the same type than
使用的类型将与
repository that find all return value so
找到所有返回值的存储库
really again everything is statically
真的，一切都是静态的
typed exactly like in Java when you are
完全像在Java中一样键入
using a class that you create in Cochin
使用您在Cochin中创建的类
you have the same novella photo
你有相同的中篇小说照片
completes
完成
but the type in France allow you to just
但法国的类型允许您
not specify the type of the return value
没有指定返回值的类型
of the parameters of a variable if if
如果变量的参数
the compiler is able to guess it
编译器可以猜测
so let's talk about how to persist the
所以我们来谈谈如何坚持
data so choosing spring data GPA is
数据，因此选择Spring 数据GPA为
perfectly fine with code clean that
完美的代码清理
works I have created a sample that you
作品我创建了一个样本给你
can see in github.com slashes the slash
可以在github.com中看到斜杠
spring would cut in the demo and that
Spring 会减少演示，
works perfectly well so nothing wrong
效果很好，所以没错
using GPA and cut clean together I want
使用GPA并一起修剪干净
to be clear about that but I would like
要清楚一点，但我想
to show you another way to write
给你展示另一种写作方式
you-you-you persistence they are more
你，你，你，坚持，他们更
lightweight way to do that more
轻巧的方式来做更多
idiomatic clean way to write that and in
惯用的简洁方式来写
order to achieve that we are going to
为了实现我们要
use exposed which is a type safe cut in
使用裸露是安全切入的类型
SQL DSL that will allow us to write SQL
SQL DSL将使我们能够编写SQL
queries in coding and I think that
查询编码，我认为
generally a good example of DSL that we
通常是DSL的一个很好的例子
can write with Kotlin that's less
可以用Kotlin进行写
powerful than in scala in scale you can
比scala更强大
write GSL that you don't understand
写你不懂的GSL
yourself even if you are writing it's
你自己，即使你在写
better even with the limitation of code
即使有代码限制也更好
clean you can really write some very
干净，你真的可以写一些非常
poor fool DSL and I think the finder
可怜的傻瓜DSL，我认为发现者
writes the right balance about that so
为此写了正确的平衡
why using a square without GPA
为什么使用没有GPA的正方形
I think that's allow you to get more
我认为这可以让您获得更多
control on the SQL queries and about the
控制SQL查询以及关于
joints that allow you to have a lighter
可以让你轻一点的关节
technology stack to take advantage of
技术堆栈以利用
the native database functionalities and
本机数据库功能和
also we we rarely need to change the
我们也很少需要改变
basis so why not just taking advantage
所以为什么不仅仅利用
about the one that you are using an
关于您正在使用的
example of interesting native
有趣的本地人的例子
functionalities for example PostgreSQL
功能，例如PostgreSQL
native JSON support in this example we
在此示例中，本机JSON支持
are creating a user's table that
正在创建一个用户表
contains values columns and one of the
包含值列和其中之一
columns metadata as a JSON the type
列元数据作为JSON类型
that'll you to insert some G's endure
那你要插入一些G的承受力
units so you see that we are inserting
单位，以便您看到我们正在插入
address with line 1 postcodes
第1行邮政编码的地址
two states fubar and the nice thing
两国富巴和好东西
about the Jesus invited because that we
关于耶稣邀请，因为我们
could do that with a regular texts Quran
可以用古兰经》来做到这一点
so Jesus and B type allow us to index to
所以耶稣和B型让我们索引到
have an index on on on the G zone
在G区域打开索引
provided directly in this column so what
直接在此列中提供的内容
that means that means that I will be
这意味着我将
able to write some statement like cell
能够写一些像细胞一样的语句
select from users when doc and opens and
在用户选择文档并打开时进行选择，然后
to put a where closest about the address
在地址附近放一个地方
and the postcode with the same speed
和邮递区号的速度相同
than if it was a native column so that
比起它是原生列
data law has to do very powerful things
数据法必须要做非常有力的事情
like that because in Java and in
之所以这样，是因为在Java和
Kathleen we are statically typed so we
凯瑟琳我们被静态键入，所以我们
are less dynamic light like in PHP or in
像PHP或in
JavaScript and where you are writing for
JavaScript和您在哪里写
example a back end a back office that
例如后端的后台
allow you to allow you to use the user
允许您允许您使用用户
to create some structure at runtime that
在运行时创建一些结构
you don't have you don't know when you
你没有你不知道你什么时候
develop the application that kind of
开发这样的应用程序
dynamic capabilities is is pretty useful
动态功能非常有用
so if if we have writen if we add
所以如果我们写的话我们添加
write-ins application with spring gdb
用Spring gdb编写应用程序
see a rigorous report we should have
看到我们应该有一份严格的报告
created a schema that SQL with that kind
创建了一种使用这种SQL的架构
of stuff that creates the tables if they
创建表的东西，如果他们
don't exist and they create the index as
不存在，他们创建索引为
if they don't exist so how we are going
如果它们不存在，那么我们将如何发展
to write that in Kirkland with exposed
写在柯克兰与暴露
in fact we are going to write SQL schema
实际上，我们将要编写SQL模式
with code in code so this this is the
与代码中的代码，所以这是
equivalent of the previous SQL code you
等效于您之前的SQL代码
see that's that's SQL attraction but
看到那是SQL的吸引力，但是
when we lightweight we directly use a
当我们轻量化时，我们直接使用
skill types we are defining that ideas
我们正在定义的技能类型
in the girl auto implemented a new
在女孩汽车实施了新的
primary key we defined the various
主键我们定义了各种
columns and
列和
the interesting thing is that these
有趣的是，这些
messages and users objects will be
消息和用户对象将是
reused after I'm going to show you that
在我要告诉你之后再使用
to write directly the queries with a
用一个直接写查询
static statically typed API so we are
静态静态类型化的API，所以我们
not using spring data in that
不使用Spring 数据
application so I'm writing quickly a
应用程序，所以我很快就写了
repository interface which contain a
存储库接口，其中包含
great table create final digital fine
伟大的表创造最终的数字罚款
Bank boutique box so that one will
银行精品盒，使一个
allowed to find some messages or user
允许查找一些消息或用户
based on specific bounding box and it
基于特定的边界框
will allow us to update the location and
将允许我们更新位置并
so Method repository and news repository
所以方法库和新闻库
extend this produces a tree
扩展产生一棵树
so if we have a look to the repository
所以如果我们看一下仓库
implementation its annotated with at
实现，其注释为
repository like a regular regular spring
像常规的常规 Spring 一样的存储库
that repository we are using a
我们正在使用的存储库
transactional because exposed support
事务性的，因为支持暴露
spring transactional in your real
真正的春季交易
application that should be on the
应该在
service layer I guess and if you have a
服务层，我想如果您有一个
look to the update location function for
寻找更新位置功能
example you will see that's exposed
示例，您将看到它被暴露
allow us to write our SQL queries with
允许我们用编写SQL查询
the cut clean type safe API that allow
允许使用的清洁类型安全API
us to about to complete anything like
我们即将完成类似
that so instead of that's a little bit
所以不是那一点
different
不同
usually we spring data you have a cred
通常我们会根据数据来证明您的信誉
credit opposite URI that you extend to
归功于您扩展到的相反URI
add you your custom ones spring that is
添加您的自定义 Spring
able to create some queries based on the
能够根据
name of the method here it's a little
方法的名称在这里有点
bit different here we are using the
有点不同，我们在使用
power of code clean and the library
代码清理和库的功能
exposed but I guess there will be a lot
暴露但我想会有很多
of other ones too at the beginning
一开始也是其他的
defines the structure of the tables and
定义表的结构，并
reusing these users or messages object
重用这些用户或消息对象
to directly write the queries with a
用一个直接写查询
statically typed API so here the queries
静态类型的API，因此这里的查询
are quite simple but in real life you
很简单，但在现实生活中
can write quite complicated statements
可以写出非常复杂的语句
with that kind of API and
使用这种API并
here that's an example that is about SQL
这是一个关于SQL的例子
but you can find the same about no SQL
但是您可以找到关于没有SQL的相同信息
HTML you can write values DSL with a
您可以使用HTML将值DSL写入HTML
Kaplan and that's that's a pretty
卡普兰，那是一个漂亮的
interesting use case I think if you have
我认为如果您有一个有趣的用例
a look to the ech function that is not
看看不是
using parenthesis that's because this
使用括号是因为
this function has been specified as in
此功能已指定为
fix and in fix just say that you can
修复和修复中只是说你可以
omit the parentheses that just would be
省略括号将
that just syntactic sugar to be able to
只是语法糖就可以
write more functional code basically but
基本上写更多的功能代码，但是
that's that's a regular function there
那是那里的常规功能
is no no magic here and so we are using
这里不是没有魔术，所以我们正在使用
SQL so that's fine but how does that
SQL，那很好，但是那怎么办
works when I have to use a native
当我必须使用本机时可以工作
functionality of my database because as
我的数据库的功能，因为
I said previously exposed is a regular
我说以前曝光是正常的
SQL library I have talked about native
我谈论过的本机SQL库
functionalities like JSON support or
JSON支持或
like geospatial support so how how could
像地理空间支持，那怎么可能
I write this within method where we're
我在我们所在的方法中编写此代码
exposed just support regular SQL so
暴露只是支持常规SQL所以
that's that's another example of code
那是另一个代码示例
clean power that's cut in extensions so
减少了扩展功能的清洁电源
curtain extensions allow you to extend
窗帘扩展允许您扩展
existing classes to add new methods
现有类中添加新方法
directly in place so that sounds a
直接就位，听起来像
little bit magic but that's that's not
一点魔力，但这不是
so magic basically you see here I define
所以魔术基本上你在这里看到我定义
a function tabled and put in extension
列出并放入扩展中的函数
table dot point that means that I'm
表格点表示我
going to add a point to the existing
将增加一个点到现有的
table type that is coming from exposed
来自暴露的表类型
so that's coming from a jar I don't own
所以那是我不拥有的罐子里出来的
that I just adding a method into that
我只是在其中添加一个方法
and and this this function will be
并且此功能将是
available when I write my code only if I
仅当我编写代码时可用
import this extension that's a little
导入这个扩展名
bit like static import
有点像静态导入
I don't know if you have used the
我不知道您是否使用过
chicken pot but it's a little bit like
鸡肉锅，但是有点像
that if I just using regular code with
如果我只是使用常规代码
no specific import table we'll just add
没有具体的导入表，我们只添加
the methods the functions defined by by
方法定义的功能
default in in this class but if I import
此类中的默认值，但如果我导入
the phylum where I have defined this
我定义这个的门
expansion type table gunpoint then the
扩展类型表枪口，然后
compiler of the IDE will propose me in
IDE的编译器会在
the autocomplete the point method and
自动完成点方法和
that's nice balance between the dynamic
动态与动态
thing because extension is quite dynamic
因为扩展是动态的
but the fact that extension are resolved
但扩展名已解决的事实
statically make that less less magic and
静态地减少魔法
keep a load to keep the control about
保持负荷以保持控制
what what what extension is because if
什么是扩展名，因为如果
we we don't add this static resolution
我们不添加此静态分辨率
if I wrote 1 unread extensions that that
如果我写了1个未读的扩展
would be not manageable so here we have
将无法管理，所以我们在这里
a look to the configuration class so
看看配置类
that's a regular spring boot
那是常规的 spring boot
configuration class annotated with
带有注释的配置类
spring good application so open keyword
Spring 很好的应用程序，所以打开关键字
is needed at class and method level
在类和方法级别是必需的
because we don't because we are using
因为我们不是因为我们正在使用
silly to extend that class internally in
愚蠢地在内部扩展该类
as of spring farm up for that free cut
从春季农场开始
injects and module is automatically draw
注入并自动绘制模块
registrated so you don't have to
已注册，因此您不必
register it in that case and using that
在这种情况下注册并使用
to register the page this module that
注册页面此模块
allowed to Jackson to deal with your
允许杰克逊处理您的
graphic types and the main function
图形类型和主要功能
don't have to be wrapped into a class
不必被包裹在一个类中
you you can put that as a top-level
您可以将其作为顶级
function that works the grader file is a
适用于平地机文件的功能是
regular one
普通人
the point specific to cut clean as cut
特定于切割的点
clean cattle plug-in that you specify
您指定的清洁牛插件
and the cleanest at the ribbon cutting
和最干净的剪彩
reflects libraries the rest is just
反映图书馆，其余的只是
regular Java dependencies I don't have
我没有的常规Java依赖项
specified that previously but you can
指定以前，但您可以
totally mix Java enter clean code into
完全混合Java输入干净的代码
the same code base that works perfectly
同样完美的代码库
well and that's that's yeah there is a
好，那就是，是的，有一个
very good inter a bit between these both
两者之间非常好
technologies recently rather we're
技术，而不是我们
announced that cut in Gradle go Scotland
宣布削减Gradle前往苏格兰
so what that means as you may know
那你可能知道什么意思
Gradle is using groovy to describe
Gradle使用groovy来形容
build.gradle file where you specify and
您在其中指定的build.gradle文件和
you configure your build and it allowed
您配置您的构建，它允许
to use groovy to to develop the plugins
使用groovy开发插件
for example that will be still supported
例如仍将受支持
of course but grader is really switching
当然，但平地机确实在切换
to Kathleen for the main languages used
给凯瑟琳（Kathleen）使用的主要语言
to describe you all your bins so they do
描述你所有的垃圾箱
this switch because as I said previously
因为我之前说过
cooking allowed to write short code
做饭允许写短代码
Layton groovy but with static typing and
Layton常规但具有静态输入和
in terms of autocomplete for example in
在自动完成方面，例如
the values I Dec autocomplete is in
我12月自动完成的值在
Gradle is just does not work basically
摇篮只是基本上不起作用
with Kathleen by default you have full
默认情况下与凯瑟琳一起
auto complete everything works and that
自动完成所有工作，
give more control about the plug-in
对插件进行更多控制
ecosystem and thing like that so that's
生态系统之类的东西
not a small or small move and with
不小的动作，
Gradle free you will see that by default
免费Gradle，您会默认看到
rather way is going to push for using
相当的方法将推动使用
Kathleen by default and they still
凯瑟琳（Kathleen）默认情况下，他们仍然
support groovy and that's perfectly fine
支持groovy，那很好
to use groovy but when you see the
使用groovy，但是当您看到
advantages in terms of autocompletes in
在自动完成方面的优势
terms of spin or so yeah that really
旋转的条件，是的，真的
makes a difference so I think that's why
有所作为，所以我认为这就是为什么
they they did the switch
他们做了切换
in term of deployments replication is a
就部署而言，复制是
regular Springwood whenever jaw
经常下颌的斯普林伍德
it's it's 18 18 megabyte so quite small
这是18 18兆字节，非常小
it's done in less than three seconds and
不到三秒钟就完成了
in terms of memory consumption it run
就内存消耗而言，它运行
with less than 32 megabytes of RAM so
少于32 MB的RAM
you see that Kathleen don't consume more
你会看到凯瑟琳不消耗更多
memory than D'Angela and when you use
记忆力比D'Angela以及使用时
some dependencies for example without
一些依赖，例如没有
idea net and GPA like I have done with
像我所做的那样，想法网和GPA
expose that is the thin layer on top of
露出那是薄薄的一层
gdb see you can run perfectly fine
gdb看到您可以完美运行
spring boots and computing application
spring boot 和计算应用
with less than 30 32 megabytes of RAM so
少于30 32 MB的内存
I won't use that in production but I
我不会在生产中使用它，但是我
think in production with with 64
用64位思考生产
that--some that's perfectly fine and
那-一点都很好并且
Catrin has been designed also for the
卡特琳（Catrin）也专为
mobile world where whether the
移动世界在哪里
constraints are quite where the rules
约束是规则所在
are quite imitated so that's also a good
非常模仿，所以这也是一个很好的
fit for for cloud application so we have
适合云应用程序，所以我们有
talked a lot about Kathleen for
谈论了很多关于凯瑟琳的事情
server-side developments I have said I
我说过服务器端的发展
have not deterred that but cooking is I
并没有阻止我做饭
think the first choice or so for Android
认为是Android的首选
development but it could also be used
开发，但也可以使用
for client-side developments so there is
用于客户端开发，因此有
a transpiler called cutting to GS that a
一个叫切成GS的堆垛机
row to compile code clean source code to
行来编译干净的源代码到
JavaScript source code I think every
我认为每一个JavaScript源代码
every language to that so differences in
每种语言的差异
terms of maturity and if it's usable in
期限，以及是否适用于
the real life
现实生活
so that's currently not released
因此目前尚未发布
in a spot as cooking one dot Oh I mean
在一个地方煮一个点哦，我的意思是
it's available but that's not tagged as
它可用，但未标记为
a projection ready that that's a target
准备好的投影，这就是目标
for cutting one that one but there is
切成一个但有一个
already produce usable and so that we
已经产生了可用的，所以我们
generate some in JavaScript with the
使用JavaScript在JavaScript中生成一些
libraries that you are using some parts
您正在使用某些零件的库
of the code clean standard library and
代码清理标准库
and your application so as I said Kalina
和您的应用程序，如我所说的Kalina
statically type so you will have to
静态输入，因此您必须
write some or you will have to use some
写一些，否则你将不得不使用一些
existing definition a little bit like in
现有的定义有点像
typescript that allow you to to use a
打字稿，使您可以使用
JavaScript libraries so in that case I'm
JavaScript库，所以在这种情况下
defining some quick quick declaration
定义一些快速的声明
for jQuery the Catalan guys are walking
jQuery的加泰罗尼亚人走了
and some converters that allow to
和一些允许
convert typescript definition to contain
将打字稿定义转换为包含
definition automatically that will allow
自动定义，将允许
you to reuse a huge number of API
您重用大量的API
definition coming from the typescript
来自打字稿的定义
world and that'll you to have
世界，那你将拥有
autocomplete compile time check sharing
自动完成编译时间检查共享
code between client side and server side
客户端和服务器端之间的代码
and also Susan opera you to have
还有苏珊歌剧
matching between both the source code
两者之间的匹配源代码
boxes basis so that's expected to be
盒子的基础上，所以预计
released really for wide usage in
真正发布用于广泛
thirteen 1.1 with module JavaScript
带有模块JavaScript的13个1.1
module support better documentation
模块支持更好的文档
between IDE integration and some Xmas
IDE集成和一些Xmas之间
scripts e6 report that works pretty well
脚本e6报告效果很好
that generates big javascript files so
会生成大的javascript文件，因此
that's not perfect and that still can
那并不完美，仍然可以
progress in term of the size of
规模的进步
javascript generated and but that that
javascript生成的，但是那
definitely doable to write an
绝对可以写一个
application with coupling for both
结合使用的应用
client side and server side but for
客户端和服务器端，但是
really for the long term I'm much more
从长远来看，我的确更多
interested in
有兴趣
saying how many of you have heard about
说你们中有多少人听说过
webassembly yeah so whether some lie is
webassembly是的，所以无论是否说谎
a really new technology so that's not
一项真正的新技术，所以不是
surprising that not everybody I've heard
令人惊讶的是，不是我听说过的每个人
about that well as some lies basically
关于那个好，基本上是一些谎言
the technology for the web by code I
通过代码I进行网络技术
mean until now we have used JavaScript
意思是直到现在我们都使用过JavaScript
as the web by code basically every
作为网络，基本上每个代码
everybody is transferring to JavaScript
每个人都在转移到JavaScript
I think the approach of transferring to
我认为转移到
JavaScript on the long-term is perfectly
JavaScript从长远来看是完美的
fine for languages that are superset of
适用于以下语言的超集
JavaScript I mean for typescript that's
JavaScript我的意思是打字稿
perfectly fine for CoffeeScript that's
非常适合CoffeeScript
perfectly fine transpiring some X my
完美的表现出一些X我的
script six or seven to previous version
脚本六到七到以前的版本
of JavaScript is also perfectly fine and
的JavaScript也很好
that will stay that ultimately compiling
最终会保留下来
some JavaScript with very different
一些JavaScript截然不同
compiling some some languages with very
用一些非常汇编的语言
different semantics than JavaScript to
与JavaScript具有不同的语义
javascript is a hack and yeah you have
javascript是一种hack，是的，
some issues like for example the numeric
一些问题，例如数字
types are not the same so even if you
类型不一样，即使您
can come close to something that works
可以接近有效的东西
you have some small differences you have
你有一些小的差异
some performance issue and that's not
一些性能问题，那不是
very native so the Biggers before so
非常原生，所以之前的Biggers
Google Apple Microsoft Mozilla has has
Google Apple Microsoft Mozilla已拥有
worked for some years now about how to
已经工作了几年了
improve the level of performance in the
提高绩效水平
browser so you may have heard about SMGs
浏览器，因此您可能听说过SMG
which is a small subset of JavaScript
这是JavaScript的一小部分
that allowed to basically compile C C++
基本上可以编译C C ++
program to this subset of JavaScript and
编程到此JavaScript子集并
run very very very fast so in that case
运行非常非常快，所以在这种情况下
they are using this subset of JavaScript
他们正在使用这部分JavaScript
as a way to describe the assembly code
作为描述汇编代码的一种方式
of the program there is Native Client
该程序的存在本机客户端
technology from Google for example there
例如Google的技术
has been that I have worked a lot of
一直以来，我已经做了很多工作
with with that at some point so
在某个时候
yeah hold this are these technologies
是的，这就是这些技术
are nice but they are not standardized
不错，但是没有标准化
and there should be a better way
而且应该有更好的方法
so this for the four major browser
所以这对于四大浏览器
vendors are working for a few months and
供应商工作了几个月，
webassembly
网络组装
which is a binary format to describe in
这是一种二进制格式，用于描述
a neutral way there's a code basically
一种中立的方式，基本上有一个代码
and the idea is to be able to make it
而且想法是能够做到
possible for the browser to execute that
浏览器可以执行
code very efficiently initially that's
最初非常有效地编码
more focused for very for application
更专注于应用
like games like compute computing
像计算计算这样的游戏
intensive application but so that made
密集的应用程序，但使
me for being a target computation for
我是作为目标计算
CCP space program but web-based online
CCP空间计划，但基于Web的在线
is also something that could be used to
也是可以用来
as a computation target for other
作为其他人的计算目标
languages so we could see rest
语言，以便我们可以看到休息
complaining to whether some rival could
抱怨一些竞争对手是否可以
see Kirkland may be opening to a decimal
看到柯克兰可能开小数
I switched etc etc and that would make
我换了等等等等，这会使
so jealous Caprice dead we stay but that
嫉妒的Caprice死了，我们留下来了，但是那
will be not an achieve very efficient
将不是一个非常有效的实现
quite low level to be able to run some
相当低的水平，可以运行一些
application and I have tried to discuss
应用程序，我试图讨论
with Kirkland guys so there is no
与柯克兰的家伙在一起，所以没有
official plan about webOS online yet but
关于webOS在线的官方计划，但是
I think that's that's an interesting way
我认为那是一种有趣的方式
of thinking about Kirkland for the
关于柯克兰的思考
client side for the future compiling a
客户端，供将来编译
language that does not share the
不共享
JavaScript semantics to JavaScript is a
JavaScript语义到JavaScript是
hack and for the long term I think that
hack，从长远来看，我认为
would be interesting I guess we will see
会很有趣，我想我们会看到
quickly rest combined into webOS online
快速休息，将其合并到webOS中
webassembly is already available in in
Webassembly已在中提供
Chrome Canary if you enable to flag and
Chrome Canary（如果您启用了标记和
you can run a video game with full speed
您可以全速运行视频游戏
and that's that's what's pretty well so
那就是那很好
they are really progressing fast on that
他们在这方面确实进步很快
and next year I think we could see well
明年我想我们会很好看的
as some - approach it by visor browser
一些-通过遮阳浏览器进行处理
without flags so that that's an
没有标志，所以这是一个
interesting technology to follow and if
有趣的技术，如果
got clean compiled - to obey sunlight
整理干净-遵守阳光
that could allow people to create a war
可能会让人们发动战争
ecosystem of complain cut clean
抱怨的生态系统干净利落
client-side libraries that would be
客户端库
different than the JavaScript ecosystem
与JavaScript生态系统不同
that we see and yeah that would be
我们看到的，是的
interesting how to learn Catalan so you
有趣的如何学习加泰罗尼亚语，所以你
can go to try that cutscene long dog you
可以去尝试那个过场的长狗
will see Catalan cones which is an
会看到加泰罗尼亚锥
application that allows you to learn
可以让您学习的应用程序
step by step language this application
逐步使用此应用程序的语言
is developed with code clean - yes for
用干净的代码开发-是的
example that's that's an example the
就是那个例子
community is very interesting the slack
社区很有趣
there is a slack instance for cocaine
可卡因有一个松弛的实例
which is very nice where you can discuss
很好，您可以在那里讨论
directly with cut-in developers so it
直接与有经验的开发人员联系
should be an interesting place to go and
应该是一个有趣的地方
I will finish by I can show just quickly
我会结束，因为我可以快速展示
a quick example demo of the application
该应用程序的快速示例演示
so so if you clones are just Bastion
因此，如果您克隆的只是堡垒
messenger you will get this application
Messenger，您将获得此应用程序
we have the message user classes
我们有消息用户类
propitiatory just what I showed you so
只是我向你展示的
to run it I just I just ran the
运行它，我只是运行了
application class
应用类别
okay so so that just an application
好，这样一个应用程序
where I can write some messages like
在这里我可以写一些消息
that okay and if I if I open another
好的，如果我打开另一个
browser and go to the van and I creates
浏览器并转到货车，我创建了
a message here the message will be
一条消息，消息将是
pushed by server sent events in two
由服务器在两个事件中发送事件
holes various instances to show that so
洞各种实例表明
that's a really simple application but
那是一个非常简单的应用程序，但是
that's just to to show you a real
只是为了向您展示真实
example of of convenience being good
方便的例子很好
application Duke back there so what next
应用程序公爵回到那里，那么下一步
in terms of confidence reports in spring
根据春季的信心报告
we are going to develop to improve the
我们将发展以改善
spring Kathleen which is cutting
Spring 凯瑟琳切
extensions for spring we are going also
Spring 的延伸，我们也要
to add some curtain extension for
为添加一些窗帘扩展
reactor that's not official project
不是官方项目的反应堆
that's a project that will be developed
这是一个将要开发的项目
mainly by me for the beginning and the
主要由我负责
community the reactor example is very
社区反应堆的例子非常
interesting because the reactive API is
有趣，因为反应式API是
like a raghava reactor front api's that
就像Raghava Reactor的api一样
you can't extend as a user you can't add
您无法以用户身份扩展，也无法添加
a method to observe a berlin eric java
观察柏林eric java的方法
you can't admit an influx in reactor and
你不能接受反应堆的涌入
here again curtain extensions really
再次在这里窗帘扩展
works pretty well because they allow you
效果很好，因为它们允许您
to add some extensions to flex or to
添加一些扩展到flex或
observable without modifying george in a
可观察而无需修改乔治
class for example we could imagine a max
例如，我们可以想象一个最大值
dot max method that will be only
最大点数法
available when we have some flux or
当我们有通量或
observer of integral of long for example
例如长整数的观察者
and that's that's an example where we
这就是我们的一个例子
can we can use some some methods on exit
我们可以在退出时使用一些方法吗
existing class and that's that's a good
现有的课程，那是一个很好的
fit with reactive api stats in java are
适用于Java中的反应式api统计信息是
not extensible at all
根本无法扩展
we are going to add some continually
我们将不断添加一些
before class report in spring framework
Spring Framework 上课前的报告
for that we are going to use information
为此，我们将使用信息
from the cut-in type system where we can
从插入式系统中，我们可以
know if variable is can could be null or
知道变量是否可以为null或
not and with that we will we will know
没有，我们将知道
if the parameter should be should be
如果参数应该是
required or not in spring MVC for
Spring MVC是否需要
example and we continue to improve the
示例，我们将继续改进
curtain integration in Springwood there
窗帘整合在斯普林伍德那里
is no really breaking point just have to
并不是真正的突破点
wait cut in one that one as I said
等我说的切成一个
previously so there is a cut in one that
以前有一个削减
one preview which bring co-routines
一个带协同例程的预览
coroutines allow you to write a
协程允许您编写一个
synchronous code without using callbacks
不使用回调的同步代码
for example for simple use cases now
例如现在简单的用例
personally I prefer using reactive API
我个人更喜欢使用反应式API
like reactor to write that that's much
像反应堆这样写
more powerful but yeah seems to think
更强大，但似乎在想
that corrosion is nice there is that is
腐蚀很好，那就是
in.net word so as soon as that that's
in.net一词，那就是
optional so that's not an issue type
可选的，所以不是问题类型
aliases are more interesting that allow
别名更有趣，允许
you to write aliases for values types
您为值类型编写别名
and this type eyelashes are replaced at
而且这种睫毛在
compile time so that this as zero cost
编译时间，使它成为零成本
in term of runtime so that's also to
在运行时方面，这也
continue to improve the readability when
继续提高可读性时
you are very long generics for example
你是很长的仿制药
you can use that to write shorter code
你可以用它来编写较短的代码
and yeah that's I like that kind of zero
是的，我喜欢那种零
cost abstractions that allow you to
成本抽象，使您能够
write better code there will be Java
编写更好的代码将有Java
Java 8 byte code generation because
Java 8字节代码生成，因为
currently contain generator a six byte
当前包含生成器的六个字节
code even if the language is much more
即使语言更多，也可以编码
powerful than Java 8 so that means that
比Java 8更强大，这意味着
with Curtin 1.1 they will be able to use
使用Curtin 1.1，他们将能够使用
a lambda bad collaborator for example to
一个lambda不好的合作者，例如
to implement to in the bytecode
在字节码中实现
instead of generating some anonymous
而不是产生一些匿名
classes salad style proxies should be
类沙拉样式代理应该
possible without open we will see but
没有开放的可能，我们将看到，但是
that that's the plan and we will have
那是计划，我们将有
much more useable cut into JavaScript
切入JavaScript更有用
compiler and the last point so that's I
编译器，最后一点就是我
have seen a few slide about that so
看到了一些幻灯片，所以
Kirkland guys seems to work on a cut in
柯克兰的家伙似乎在努力工作
native initiative that hold the load to
承担责任的本地倡议
compile code clean - Nate native code
编译代码干净-Nate本机代码
thanks to an LLVM back end so that's
多亏了LLVM后端，所以
Vedas time compilation that's designed
吠陀经时间编译
for lightweight runtime to target
针对轻量级运行时
embedded IOT I us sing like that and
我们像这样唱歌的嵌入式物联网
that could be maybe a bridge to weather
那可能是通往天气的桥梁
some light since the web Assam like guy
网络上的一些光阿萨姆邦像家伙
are walking on LLVM to a Bassam lie
在LLVM上走到巴萨姆的谎言
compulsion so as soon as you are able to
强迫，所以只要你能够
generate weather some light code
生成天气代码
intermediate code you are able to
您能够使用的中间代码
generate some web assembly code so why
生成一些Web汇编代码，为什么
not using that to generate reverse
不使用它来产生反向
online we'd say that's the end of the
在网上我们会说这是结束
presentation if you have some question
演示文稿，如果您有任何问题
I'm I'm available to answer Thanks
我可以回答谢谢
excuse me into the G IDE yeah as a
对不起，我是G IDE
result so an eclipse plug-in say Vince
结果是一个eclipse插件说Vince
I'm not sure I don't think there is
我不确定我认为没有
something really usable but in GDG ID
确实有用但在GDG ID中
and Eclipse are both use able to to
和Eclipse都可以使用
write code in code and obviously the
用代码写代码，显然
better the better support is in IntelliJ
更好，更好的支持是在IntelliJ中
IDE but that's not a surprise
IDE，但这不足为奇
yeah
是的
yeah it will work so it will work in
是的，它将起作用，因此它将起作用
spring tour Suites because it's based on
春季游套房，因为它基于
a clip so yeah yeah that's what that
一个剪辑，是的，是的，那个
will work pretty well okay thanks
会很好的工作，谢谢
you
您